softwarefindr.com 2018-03-25

# Privacy Policy | SoftwareFindr

This privacy policy outlines how the types of personal information is received and collected by wpmultiverse and how it is used.

 **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites wpmultiverse makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies**

wpmultiverse uses cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on wpmultiverse. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to wpmultiverse and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Clickbank and Amazon.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on wpmultiverse send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. wpmultiverse has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. wpmultiverse’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **Affiliate / Monetization / FTC Disclosure**

Softwarefindr.com, may sometimes get paid if you click one of those links and purchase a product or service. In the case of our comments, any links or recommendations are being posted by our community and do not represent endorsements by this site. In the case of our news stories, we may offer direct links to stores and vendors for the convenience of our readers, but unless otherwise stated, do not necessarily represent endoresements to those products.
